[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1981 movie The Evil Dead, the real cabin that the 5 college students stay in is located in North Carolina.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Doctor Zhivago is a character from a novel of the same name by Boris Pasternak. This is the historical background of the story in the book.", "correct_answer": "Russian Revolution", "incorrect_answers": ["The USSRs collapse", "WWII", "Brezhnevs reign"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1.5 million square mile area, known as the Bermuda Triangle, has its equivalent in the Pacific ocean. What is it called?", "correct_answer": "Devils Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Satans Triangle", "Dark Triangle", "Triangle of Death"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is characteristic of Rabbit, a fictional character in the series Winnie the Pooh?", "correct_answer": "Busy and responsible", "incorrect_answers": ["Bouncing and confident", "Gloomy and pessimistic", "Ashamed of being small"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sea borders Egypt to the east?", "correct_answer": "Red Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Black Sea", "Yellow Sea", "Mediterranean Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This quote is from what 1978 cult favorite? \nFat, drunk and stupid is no way to go through life son.", "correct_answer": "Animal House", "incorrect_answers": ["American Graffiti", "Revenge of the Nerds", "Porkys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie National Treasure, what does Ben do to Jon Voights character, before leaving with the Declaration of Independence?", "correct_answer": "Ties him up with duct tape", "incorrect_answers": ["Drugs him", "Knocks him over the head", "Locks him in the closet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Just like humans, apes and dolphins, elephants can recognize themselves in a mirror.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What company sold the first quartz wristwatch?", "correct_answer": "Seiko", "incorrect_answers": ["Bulova", "Omega", "Casio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these types of food do rabbits prefer to include  in their daily diet?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Grass", "Leafy weeds", "Forbs (such as sunflowers)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An adult salivates this much per day, on average.", "correct_answer": "1 liter (1/4 gallons)", "incorrect_answers": ["2 liters (1/2 gallons)", "0.1 liters (0.026gallons)", "1.2 liters (0.32 gallons)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Color Purple, what does Shug say will happen if you walk by a field of purple and dont notice it?", "correct_answer": "It makes God angry.", "incorrect_answers": ["The color will fade.", "You will miss a blessing.", "Bees will sting you."]}]